[
   
    {
        "question": "What is the lowest temperature ever recorded in Nepal?",
        "option1": "-40째C",
        "option2": "-32째C",
        "option3": "-42째C",
        "option4": "-56째C",
        "correctAns": "option4",
        "level": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the first female pilot of Nepal?",
        "option1": "Sugam Singh",
        "option2": "Dinesh Thapa",
        "option3": "Priya Adhikari",
        "option4": "Bhawana Rana",
        "correctAns": "option3",
        "level": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the length of Nepal's longest suspension bridge?",
        "option1": "2,128 meters",
        "option2": "3,384 meters",
        "option3": "1,426 meters",
        "option4": "4,642 meters",
        "correctAns": "option3",
        "level": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the first female CA of Nepal?",
        "option1": "Siddhi Kumari",
        "option2": "Binita Joshi",
        "option3": "Ganga G.C",
        "option4": "Sumitra Thapaliya",
        "correctAns": "option2",
        "level": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the deepest gorge in Nepal?",
        "option1": "Kali Gandaki Gorge",
        "option2": "Bheri Gorge",
        "option3": "Sunkoshi Gorge",
        "option4": "Dudh Koshi Gorge",
        "correctAns": "option1",
        "level": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the first movie theater of Nepal?",
        "option1": "Kathmandu",
        "option2": "Birgunj",
        "option3": "Pokhara",
        "option4": "Biratnagar",
        "correctAns": "option4",
        "level": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the elevation of Nepal's lowest point?",
        "option1": "60 meters",
        "option2": "70 meters",
        "option3": "80 meters",
        "option4": "90 meters",
        "correctAns": "option3",
        "level": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the first Miss Nepal?",
        "option1": "Sahana Bajracharya",
        "option2": "Ruby Rana",
        "option3": "Anuradha Koirala",
        "option4": "Rubi Gurung",
        "correctAns": "option2",
        "level": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main source of income of Mustang district?",
        "option1": "Tourism",
        "option2": "Agriculture",
        "option3": "Remittance",
        "option4": "Trade",
        "correctAns": "option1",
        "level": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the oldest university of Nepal?",
        "option1": "Tribhuvan University",
        "option2": "Kathmandu University",
        "option3": "Pokhara University",
        "option4": "Nepal Sanskrit University",
        "correctAns": "option4",
        "level": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the first person to reach the peak of Annapurna I?",
        "option1": "Maurice Herzog",
        "option2": "Reinhold Messner",
        "option3": "Edmund Hillary",
        "option4": "Tenzing Norgay",
        "correctAns": "option1",
        "level": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many national parks are there in Nepal (as of September 2017)?",
        "option1": "8",
        "option2": "21",
        "option3": "12",
        "option4": "31",
        "correctAns": "option3",
        "level": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which district is known as the 'Queen of Hills'?",
        "option1": "Ilam",
        "option2": "Dhankuta",
        "option3": "Kavre",
        "option4": "Sindhupalchowk",
        "correctAns": "option1",
        "level": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which district is Lead's mine situated?",
        "option1": "Kathmandu",
        "option2": "Baglung",
        "option3": "Rasuwa",
        "option4": "Lamjung",
        "correctAns": "option2",
        "level": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the nearest seaport from Nepal?",
        "option1": "Mumbai Seaport",
        "option2": "Chittagong Seaport",
        "option3": "Kolkata Seaport",
        "option4": "Visakhapatnam Seaport",
        "correctAns": "option3",
        "level": "2"
    }
]
